resume.md 1/12/2022

Dylan Wesenberg—Android Developer

dylan.wesenberg@gmail.com | LinkedIn | 920.312.2294 | Madison, WI

Summary

Android developer with experience in all facets of the software design process. Passionate for creating awesome user experiences for every user of an app, even if they're using accessibility tools. I love to ensure confidence in my apps through thorough testing practices and strong CI/CD pipeline checks. I ensure maintainability and extensibility of my code through careful code design and thorough documentation of public interfaces.

Experience

Nelnet—Android Developer

02/2018-Present | Experienced in Android development in Kotlin, following Android design and architecture best practices to build a new Android app. Utilized Android libraries and Architecture Components along with Material Design. Focused on accessibility and user experience. Experienced with Gitlab and Github pipelines, Gradle, CI/CD and testing. Also designed supporting RESTful apis backing the mobile apps.

Great Lakes—Android Developer

05/2015-02/2018 | Improved and maintained the customer-facing Android app while modernizing the supporting RESTful apis. Monitored customer feedback and analytics to drive the vision for our mobile apps. Also supported and maintained the customer facing website stack, including Java backend and HTML/CSS/JavaScript frontend code.

Internships

Dealerfire—Summer 2014 | Web developer intern with Dealerfire constructing webpages for car dealerships. Focusing on backend CMS as well as front-end HTML/CSS/JS and SEO optimization.

Great Lakes—Summer 2013 | Java Developer Intern with Great Lakes supporting the full stack of the borrower website in Spring/Java. Created an internal CMS tool user interface for static content.

Education

University of Wisconsin—Platteville

Software Engineering B.S. 2010-2015

Skills/Technologies

Android, Kotlin, MVVM, Android Architacture Components, W3C Accessibility, Material Design, Gradle, CI/CD, Shell Scripts, Testing, Nodejs, Typescrypt, Docker, Git, Java, Spring, RESTful apis.